…a motion picture for everyone
Longtime Companion is a drama, romance film directed by Norman René.
During the summer of 1981, a group of friends in New York are
completely unprepared for the onslaught of AIDS.
What starts as a rumor about a mysterious "gay cancer" soon turns into a major crisis as, one by one,
some of the friends begin to fall ill, leaving the others to panic about who will be next.
As death takes its toll, the lives of these friends are forever redefined
by an unconditional display of love, hope and courage.
David, played by Bruce Davison.
Willy, played by Campbell Scott.
Howard, played by Patrick Cassidy.
Lisa, played by Mary-Louise Parker.
Fuzzy, played by Stephen Caffrey.
John, played by Dermot Mulroney.
Longtime Companion is a 1989 American romantic drama film directed by Norman René and
starring Bruce Davison, Campbell Scott, Patrick Cassidy, and Mary-Louise Parker.
The first wide-release theatrical film to deal with the subject of AIDS, the film takes its title from the euphemism The New
York Times used during the 1980s to describe the surviving same-sex partner of someone who had died of AIDS.
The film explores themes of aids, politics, homophobia, hiv, death of lover.
The tone is emotional.